<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LudoLoon Studio - blog</title><link href="https://ludoloon.studio/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://ludoloon.studio/feeds/blog.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://ludoloon.studio/</id><updated>2022-02-06T14:15:51-06:00</updated><entry><title>Flight Sim Portraits</title><link href="https://ludoloon.studio/blog/flight-sim-portraits/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-01-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-02-06T14:15:51-06:00</updated><author><name>LudoLoon Studio</name></author><id>tag:ludoloon.studio,2022-01-20:/blog/flight-sim-portraits/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I started a project to practice making music. What better way than by recording a game I'm already sinking hundreds of hours into!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="position:relative;padding-bottom:56.25%;"&gt;
 &lt;iframe style="width:100%;height:100%;position:absolute;left:0px;top:0px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?list=PLL06MmY4OQnZJtHTVJ4IlCetgx6wgS_b6" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've recently shifted my focus to working on my music more seriously. My goal is to start producing custom music for video games (and beyond), but at the moment I don't have much to show off for LudoLoon Studio since it's a new project. So to build up a little portfolio, and more importantly skill, I've decided to start making music to scenes I record from playing Microsoft Flight Simulator 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those unaware, Flight Sim 2020 is basically the most photorealistic flight simulator released to date. Literally the whole world is available to explore via satellite imagery, AI generated buildings, trees, etc. If you think it's immersive on a screen, try VR! lol. It's pretty epic to say the least. Most importantly, I already play it a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can imagine, it doesn't actually have any music outside of some select discovery flight locations and menus. So it's a pretty good way to explore adding music to suit a visual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combine the fact that I like the game, need some practice "vibe matching", and just need to make more music in general to get in the groove of becoming a regular producer again, that's why I'm putting together these videos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like them, please share!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog"></category><category term="music"></category></entry><entry><title>LudoLoon Studio Redesign</title><link href="https://ludoloon.studio/blog/website-redesign/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-09-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-01-23T19:09:07-06:00</updated><author><name>LudoLoon Studio</name></author><id>tag:ludoloon.studio,2021-09-16:/blog/website-redesign/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've decided to update this site in preparation of focusing on becoming a video game music composer. More to come!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've recently decided to pursue my passion for music more seriously instead of game design. I've updated the placeholder website design that was just a landing page into this current one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's pretty much it! Keep an eye out for more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog"></category><category term="music"></category></entry></feed>